{"Answer": "Changes in Diet and Lifestyle and Long-Term Weight Gain in Women and Men\n\nSpecific dietary and other lifestyle behaviors may affect the success of the straightforward-sounding strategy `` eat less and exercise more '' for preventing long-term weight gain .\n\nWe performed prospective investigations involving three separate cohorts that included 120,877 U.S. women and men who were free of chronic diseases and not obese at baseline , with follow-up periods from 1986 to 2006 , 1991 to 2003 , and 1986 to 2006 . The relationships between changes in lifestyle factors and weight change were evaluated at 4-year intervals , with multivariable adjustments made for age , baseline body-mass index for each period , and all lifestyle factors simultaneously . Cohort-specific and sex-specific results were similar and were pooled with the use of an inverse-variance -- weighted meta-analysis .\n\nWithin each 4-year period , participants gained an average of 3.35 lb ( 5th to 95th percentile , \u2212 4.1 to 12.4 ) . On the basis of increased daily servings of individual dietary components , 4-year weight change was most strongly associated with the intake of potato chips ( 1.69 lb ) , potatoes ( 1.28 lb ) , sugar-sweetened beverages ( 1.00 lb ) , unprocessed red meats ( 0.95 lb ) , and processed meats ( 0.93 lb ) and was inversely associated with the intake of vegetables ( \u2212 0.22 lb ) , whole grains ( \u2212 0.37 lb ) , fruits ( \u2212 0.49 lb ) , nuts ( \u2212 0.57 lb ) , and yogurt ( \u2212 0.82 lb ) ( P \u2264 0.005 for each comparison ) . Aggregate dietary changes were associated with substantial differences in weight change ( 3.93 lb across quintiles of dietary change ) . Other lifestyle factors were also independently associated with weight change ( P ( 0.001 ) , including physical activity ( \u2212 1.76 lb across quintiles ) ; alcohol use ( 0.41 lb per drink per day ) , smoking ( new quitters , 5.17 lb ; former smokers , 0.14 lb ) , sleep ( more weight gain with ( 6 or ) 8 hours of sleep ) , and television watching ( 0.31 lb per hour per day ) .\n\nSpecific dietary and lifestyle factors are independently associated with long-term weight gain , with a substantial aggregate effect and implications for strategies to prevent obesity . ( Funded by the National Institutes of Health and others . )\n\n", "Topic": "diet", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "level": 0, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"], "u.s.": ["Participants"], "free of chronic disease": ["Participants"], "not obese": ["Participants"], "4-year": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"], "u.s.": ["Location"], "free of chronic disease": ["Condition"], "not obese": ["Condition"], "4-year": ["Duration"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Age": [], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Intensity": [], "Control": [], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Effect-strength": [], "Adverse-effects": [], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}, "Count": 1}, "Doggos_text": {"Sex": "The study was performed in women and men.", "Condition": "The participants were free of chronic diseases and not obese at the beginning of the study.", "Location": "The participants were from the United States of America.", "Sample-size": "There were 120,877 participants.", "Intervention-general": "The study assessed the impact of different dietary and life style factors.", "Duration": "The effects were evaluated at 4 year intervals.", "Outcomes-general": "The study measured long-term weight loss.", "Conclusion-general": "Specific dietary lifestyle factors are independently associated with long-term weight gain."}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296", "children": [{"Answer": "Losing weight is not always as simple as eating less and exercising more. It can be affected by diet and lifestyle choices. A recent study that took place over the course of twenty years has shown this. The study started out with a large sample size of participants who were free of chronic diseases and not obese and followed up with them every four years. On average, participants gained a little over 3 pounds in each four year time period. Weight increase correlated the most with eating potato chips, potatoes, sugary beverages, unprocessed red meat and processed meat. On the other hand, eating vegetables, whole grains, fruits, nuts and yogurt were all correlated with weight loss. Lifestyle factors also had an impact on the participants' weights. Physical activity was correlated with weight loss while alcohol use, smoking, not getting enough sleep and watching tv were all correlated with weight gain. ", "AssignmentId": "31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "APGX2WZ59OWDN", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"], "free of chronic disease": ["Participants"], "not obese": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"], "free of chronic disease": ["Condition"], "not obese": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2", "children": [{"Answer": "A recent 20-yr study confirmed weight loss is affected by diet and lifestyle. A large sample of persons free of chronic diseases and obesity enrolled with a follow-up every four years. Those who ate sugary and starchy foods, chips, unprocessed red meat and processed meat, and had poor lifestyle choices such as alcohol use, smoking, and lack of sleep, lost the least amount of weight. Those who ate veggies, whole grains, fruits, nuts, and yogurt, and exercised, lost the most. On avg, participants gained slightly more than 3lbs every four years. ", "AssignmentId": "39O5D9O87UDL4C1T6Y12KOR1XC73CE", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2", "WorkerId": "AGHKGWDYPVDFE", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"], "free of chronic disease": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"], "free of chronic disease": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2_39O5D9O87UDL4C1T6Y12KOR1XC73CE", "children": [{"Answer": "Weight loss is affected by diet/lifestyle as confirmed by a recent study. Diets including sugary and starchy foods (and certain meats) along with poor lifestyle lost the least amount of weight. Healthy foods (veggies, etc.) and exercise contributed to greater weight loss.", "AssignmentId": "3EFE17QCRDQG51XOI5G43NWT35XSHX", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2_39O5D9O87UDL4C1T6Y12KOR1XC73CE", "WorkerId": "A18V6K2TMWMSWD", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2_39O5D9O87UDL4C1T6Y12KOR1XC73CE_3EFE17QCRDQG51XOI5G43NWT35XSHX", "children": [{"Answer": "A recent study showed diets rich in sugary/starchy foods led to less weight loss than healthy foods and exercise. ", "AssignmentId": "34HJIJKLP6H2LHQXXT1QKL7WX9IV46", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2_39O5D9O87UDL4C1T6Y12KOR1XC73CE_3EFE17QCRDQG51XOI5G43NWT35XSHX", "WorkerId": "A1L82EA5PNL5RO", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "40-60", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2_39O5D9O87UDL4C1T6Y12KOR1XC73CE_3EFE17QCRDQG51XOI5G43NWT35XSHX_34HJIJKLP6H2LHQXXT1QKL7WX9IV46", "children": [{"Answer": "Eating sugary/starchy foods leads to less weight loss.", "AssignmentId": "3OXV7EAXLFBWOVSSW7OZYOZR2WP36S", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2_39O5D9O87UDL4C1T6Y12KOR1XC73CE_3EFE17QCRDQG51XOI5G43NWT35XSHX_34HJIJKLP6H2LHQXXT1QKL7WX9IV46", "WorkerId": "A9BVDYQU2VTIJ", "Qualification": 0.7222222222222222, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"weight loss": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_31LVTDXBL8V6QIG1U1VX55K4XGJRL2_39O5D9O87UDL4C1T6Y12KOR1XC73CE_3EFE17QCRDQG51XOI5G43NWT35XSHX_34HJIJKLP6H2LHQXXT1QKL7WX9IV46_3OXV7EAXLFBWOVSSW7OZYOZR2WP36S"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "While many have heard the advice \"eat less and exercise more\" when it comes to advice for losing weight, a research study has shown that long-term weight gain can be hard to control. Over 100,000 men and women in the United States free of obesity and chronic disease were investigated in terms of their eating habits and lifestyle changes over time. Over the four year period in which the investigation took place, participants gained around 3.35 pounds. This weight gain can be attributed to a higher intake of potato and potato products such as chips, sugar sweetened beverages, and both unprocessed and processed meat. A higher consumption of healthier foods such as vegetables, fruits, and whole grains could be attributed to weight loss. Lifestyle changes were investigated as well, and reduction in physical activity, smoking, alcohol use, sleeping habits, and watching television could all be attributed to weight gain as well as the participants dietary habits. ", "AssignmentId": "3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2ZQVXEOBZBOEF", "Qualification": 0.9444444444444444, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH", "children": [{"Answer": "Long-term weight gain can be hard to control. Over 100,000 people in the USA free of obesity and chronic disease were investigated for their eating habits and lifestyle changes over a 4 year period. They gained about 3.35 pounds, which can be attributed to a higher intake of potato products, sugary drinks, and meat, as well as reduction in physical activity, smoking, drinking, and watching television. Eating more vegetables, fruits, and whole grains can be attributed to weight loss. ", "AssignmentId": "32KTQ2V7RE0KS0200WWQEXZZRIK9MI", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH", "WorkerId": "A3SGR153YCJ1XN", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "15-24", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "A", "B"], "Intervention": ["B", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["B"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH_32KTQ2V7RE0KS0200WWQEXZZRIK9MI", "children": [{"Answer": "There are many factors that can cause long-term weight gain, including eating starchy foods and sugary drinks, smoking and watching television. Factors that can promote weight loss include increased physical activity and eating vegetables, fruits and whole grains. ", "AssignmentId": "3I33IC7ZWGN8QF8CIKR6VJWLSG9A22", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH_32KTQ2V7RE0KS0200WWQEXZZRIK9MI", "WorkerId": "A1Y22RY2G8RBAG", "Qualification": 0.8333333333333334, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"weight loss": ["Outcomes"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH_32KTQ2V7RE0KS0200WWQEXZZRIK9MI_3I33IC7ZWGN8QF8CIKR6VJWLSG9A22", "children": [{"Answer": "Eating poorly and an unhealthy lifestyle can cause long term weight gain.  To lose weight, increase exercise and eat healthy foods.", "AssignmentId": "3GU1KF0O4JM91WEAQW2EM7OKLD4BPD", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH_32KTQ2V7RE0KS0200WWQEXZZRIK9MI_3I33IC7ZWGN8QF8CIKR6VJWLSG9A22", "WorkerId": "A5R0NQCWSPEJ9", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH_32KTQ2V7RE0KS0200WWQEXZZRIK9MI_3I33IC7ZWGN8QF8CIKR6VJWLSG9A22_3GU1KF0O4JM91WEAQW2EM7OKLD4BPD", "children": [{"Answer": "Eat health and exercise to lose weight and avoid an unhealthy lifestyle.", "AssignmentId": "3LRKMWOKB629RNGKUC75CCNU1MLZ23", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH_32KTQ2V7RE0KS0200WWQEXZZRIK9MI_3I33IC7ZWGN8QF8CIKR6VJWLSG9A22_3GU1KF0O4JM91WEAQW2EM7OKLD4BPD", "WorkerId": "A9BVDYQU2VTIJ", "Qualification": 0.7222222222222222, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A79GPKH_32KTQ2V7RE0KS0200WWQEXZZRIK9MI_3I33IC7ZWGN8QF8CIKR6VJWLSG9A22_3GU1KF0O4JM91WEAQW2EM7OKLD4BPD_3LRKMWOKB629RNGKUC75CCNU1MLZ23"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Dietary and other lifestyle behaviors may affect the success of \"eat less; exercise more\" weight management strategies.\r\rInvestigations were performed in 3 groups of 120,000 U.S. non-obese men and women free of chronic diseases with follow-ups from 1986 to 2006, 1991 to 2003, and 1986 to 2006, evaluating changes in lifestyle factors and weight change at 4 year intervals. Adjustments were made for age, baseline BMI for each period, and all lifestyle factors. Results were similar among each group and sex.\r\rParticipants gained an average of 3.35 lb over each 4 year period. Weight increase was most associated with increased consumption of potato chips, potatoes, sweetened drinks, unprocessed red meats, and processed meats. It was inversely associated with consumption of vegetables, whole grains, fruits, nuts,  and yogurt. Physical activity, alcohol use, smoking, sleep, and television use were also linked with weight change..", "AssignmentId": "3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A3CFULTNTVCYE2", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "u.s.": ["Participants"], "free of chronic disease": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "u.s.": ["Location"], "free of chronic disease": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN", "children": [{"Answer": "In a clinical research trial determining dietary and other lifestyle behaviors in weight management, investigations were done among 120,000 non-obese men and women that were free of chronic disease and from the US. Evaluations of changes in lifestyles and weight changes were performed every 4 years between the years 1986-2006, 1991-2003, and 1986-2006. Participants gained 3.35 lbs every 4 years. Weight increase was more prevalent in those that did not eat as healthy. Stress, alcohol use, physical activity and smoking influenced weight change.", "AssignmentId": "3EKVH9QMEZP6OMBO2UI8LK4RCYFD29", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN", "WorkerId": "A1CYGMPC6W59KK", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "free of chronic disease": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "free of chronic disease": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN_3EKVH9QMEZP6OMBO2UI8LK4RCYFD29", "children": [{"Answer": "In a study to measure diet and lifestyle behaviors for weight management, researchers found that weight increased more by those who watch television, eat starchy foods and drink sugary drinks. There was a decrease in weight for those who exercise and eat vegetables. ", "AssignmentId": "3ZOTGHDK5JWQXIJBMIBUNWTUFRHSOR", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN_3EKVH9QMEZP6OMBO2UI8LK4RCYFD29", "WorkerId": "A1Y22RY2G8RBAG", "Qualification": 0.8333333333333334, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "man": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "man": ["Sex"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN_3EKVH9QMEZP6OMBO2UI8LK4RCYFD29_3ZOTGHDK5JWQXIJBMIBUNWTUFRHSOR", "children": [{"Answer": "Researchers found that people who eat poorly and are sedentary gained weight over time; healthier people lost weight.", "AssignmentId": "3NKQQ8O39ZQF8YKQLESER3ZJWF8DUI", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN_3EKVH9QMEZP6OMBO2UI8LK4RCYFD29_3ZOTGHDK5JWQXIJBMIBUNWTUFRHSOR", "WorkerId": "A5R0NQCWSPEJ9", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN_3EKVH9QMEZP6OMBO2UI8LK4RCYFD29_3ZOTGHDK5JWQXIJBMIBUNWTUFRHSOR_3NKQQ8O39ZQF8YKQLESER3ZJWF8DUI", "children": [{"Answer": "People who don't exercise or eat healthy are less likely to lose weight.", "AssignmentId": "3EFVCAY5L4UUDND5S7DKY9C74NY8JQ", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN_3EKVH9QMEZP6OMBO2UI8LK4RCYFD29_3ZOTGHDK5JWQXIJBMIBUNWTUFRHSOR_3NKQQ8O39ZQF8YKQLESER3ZJWF8DUI", "WorkerId": "AZBZBTTME3HAI", "Qualification": 0.8333333333333334, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3RYC5T2D74EWH3VZMTO4MMTO25FPRN_3EKVH9QMEZP6OMBO2UI8LK4RCYFD29_3ZOTGHDK5JWQXIJBMIBUNWTUFRHSOR_3NKQQ8O39ZQF8YKQLESER3ZJWF8DUI_3EFVCAY5L4UUDND5S7DKY9C74NY8JQ"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Long term weight gain was seen in men and women across the board wen a twenty year study was done. The study looked at 120,877 men and women who were not over weight nor had chronic health conditions at the beginning. Every 4 years individuals were evaluated and adjustments were made for age, baseline body mass index and lifestyle factors. \r\rAn interesting component to the diet study was the increase of processed foods to the diets of the participants. This significantly increased weight gain for those people who weighed in every four years. Processed foods considered were potato chips, potatoes, soda pop and unprocessed red meats. an average of 3.5 pounds over the 4 year period were gained. Or one pound a year on average. If these individuals ate a significant amount of vegetables, whole grains, fruits, nuts and yogurt one could help alleviate that gain. The study also concluded that for people who smoked or were former smokers they also gained a bit weight. The study ended by saying if several of these factors were watched, obesity could be avoided. ", "AssignmentId": "3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A2LTOS0AZ3B28A", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR", "children": [{"Answer": "20 year study on long term weight gain looked at 120,877 men and women not overweight or with chronic health conditions. Evaluations and adjustments every 4 years  for baseline BMI and lifestyle factors. An increase in processed foods (chips, potatoes etc.) in their diets increased weight gain. Average of 3.5 lbs over 4 years. If these people ate better and included vegetables, whole grain, fruit and nuts they could help alleviate the gain. Smokers and former smokers gained weight. If factors are watched, obesity can be avoided.  ", "AssignmentId": "3DPNQGW4LM0H6RBWWLTI8TRXFQP465", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR", "WorkerId": "AOHQSD0GH8HTE", "Qualification": 0.8333333333333334, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR_3DPNQGW4LM0H6RBWWLTI8TRXFQP465", "children": [{"Answer": "A 20 year study on weight gain found increased intake of processed food led to more weight gain.  This weight gain could be avoided by eating more vegetables, whole grains, fruit and nuts.  Regarding smokers, both current and former smokers gained weight in the study.", "AssignmentId": "3HSYG7LRBKJ9J8LOJHAZPTLBESQKKE", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR_3DPNQGW4LM0H6RBWWLTI8TRXFQP465", "WorkerId": "A3BDVHNMJECSKG", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR_3DPNQGW4LM0H6RBWWLTI8TRXFQP465_3HSYG7LRBKJ9J8LOJHAZPTLBESQKKE", "children": [{"Answer": "A study on weight gain found a correlation with the quantity of processed food intake. Eating more healthy food reversed this effect.", "AssignmentId": "33CID57105EE7GVZJBU1N7HOSBSL30", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR_3DPNQGW4LM0H6RBWWLTI8TRXFQP465_3HSYG7LRBKJ9J8LOJHAZPTLBESQKKE", "WorkerId": "A18V6K2TMWMSWD", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR_3DPNQGW4LM0H6RBWWLTI8TRXFQP465_3HSYG7LRBKJ9J8LOJHAZPTLBESQKKE_33CID57105EE7GVZJBU1N7HOSBSL30", "children": [{"Answer": "Eating more processed food causes weight gain. Healthy food is the opposite", "AssignmentId": "3Z9WI9EOZ09IHIKGDW72C15JMWRKHL", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR_3DPNQGW4LM0H6RBWWLTI8TRXFQP465_3HSYG7LRBKJ9J8LOJHAZPTLBESQKKE_33CID57105EE7GVZJBU1N7HOSBSL30", "WorkerId": "A9BVDYQU2VTIJ", "Qualification": 0.7222222222222222, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3COPXFW7XCXAUZI4W9F7LA7A7DNKPR_3DPNQGW4LM0H6RBWWLTI8TRXFQP465_3HSYG7LRBKJ9J8LOJHAZPTLBESQKKE_33CID57105EE7GVZJBU1N7HOSBSL30_3Z9WI9EOZ09IHIKGDW72C15JMWRKHL"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "Lifestyle changes, including what a person eats, may prevent weight gain over a long period of time.\r\rThree separate investigations of 120,877 people took place between 1986 and 2006.  Each person wasn't obese and did not suffer from a chronic illness.  Changes in lifestyles and weight change occurred every four years.  Every four years the average weight gain was 3.35 pounds.  Increased weight gain occurred most frequently with the intake of starchy foods, sugar-sweetened foods, unprocessed red meat, and processed meat.  Decreased weight gain was observed most frequently with eating vegetables, while grains, fruits, nuts, and yogurt.  Participants who took part in physical activities lost weight.  Those who drank alcohol, smoked, slept more than 6 hours, or watched television also gained weight.\r\rThe study as a whole proved that specific dietary and lifestyle factors do affect long-term weigh gain.", "AssignmentId": "34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A1E66M679AFI3S", "Qualification": 0.7222222222222222, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"], "not obese": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"], "not obese": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "A", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD", "children": [{"Answer": "According to a study of 120,877 people, lifestyle changes may prevent weight gain.  Between 1986 and 2006, healthy people were examined every four years.  The average weight gain during the four years was 3.35 pounds.  Increased weight correlated with intake of starchy food, meat, alcohol, smoking, people who sleep more than 6 hours, and tv watchers.  Decreased weight was seen with a vegetarian diet.  Overall, the study shows that specific dietary and lifestyle factors affect long-term weight gain.", "AssignmentId": "3DR23U6WE6Z50RJ1H4DOSPV2CNSETU", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD", "WorkerId": "A2C4VDQC5HQ1YP", "Qualification": 0.8333333333333334, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["B"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD_3DR23U6WE6Z50RJ1H4DOSPV2CNSETU", "children": [{"Answer": "A study running from 1986 to 2006 found that lifestyle correlates with long-term weight gain.  More starchy food and meat, more alcohol, smoking, more sleep, and more TV watching were all associated with more weight gain.  Vegetarianism correlated with lower weight.", "AssignmentId": "3OB0CAO74IAD1N9XHB8TL9KUKQTYHH", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD_3DR23U6WE6Z50RJ1H4DOSPV2CNSETU", "WorkerId": "A3BDVHNMJECSKG", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "long term": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD_3DR23U6WE6Z50RJ1H4DOSPV2CNSETU_3OB0CAO74IAD1N9XHB8TL9KUKQTYHH", "children": [{"Answer": "A link between lifestyle and weight gain was found in a study. Diet was one of the factors. Less weight was found with a vegetarian diet.", "AssignmentId": "3LBXNTKX0SGVMC14E3YZPEFXZC59XK", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD_3DR23U6WE6Z50RJ1H4DOSPV2CNSETU_3OB0CAO74IAD1N9XHB8TL9KUKQTYHH", "WorkerId": "A18V6K2TMWMSWD", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD_3DR23U6WE6Z50RJ1H4DOSPV2CNSETU_3OB0CAO74IAD1N9XHB8TL9KUKQTYHH_3LBXNTKX0SGVMC14E3YZPEFXZC59XK", "children": [{"Answer": "A vegetarian diet is more effective in weight loss than others.", "AssignmentId": "3CP1TO84PUMBK9WVNO0PN8GZ0MB52Y", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD_3DR23U6WE6Z50RJ1H4DOSPV2CNSETU_3OB0CAO74IAD1N9XHB8TL9KUKQTYHH_3LBXNTKX0SGVMC14E3YZPEFXZC59XK", "WorkerId": "AZBZBTTME3HAI", "Qualification": 0.8333333333333334, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "weight loss": ["Outcomes-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_34Z02EIMITY691479XE970TYIJ70TD_3DR23U6WE6Z50RJ1H4DOSPV2CNSETU_3OB0CAO74IAD1N9XHB8TL9KUKQTYHH_3LBXNTKX0SGVMC14E3YZPEFXZC59XK_3CP1TO84PUMBK9WVNO0PN8GZ0MB52Y"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "We performed prospective investigations involving 2 seperate cohorts that included 120,877 U.S. genders who were free of chronic diseases & not obese @ baseline.  W/follow up times of 1986-2006, 1991-2003, 1986-2006. The relationships of changed lifestyle factors & weight were evaluated @ 4 yr intervals w/multivariable adjustments mad for age, baseline body mass index for each period & all lifestyle factors simultaneiously cohort & sex specific results were similar.  Within each 4yr period they gained an average of 3.35 lbs on the basis of increased daily servings of individual dietary components.  4 yr change was most strongly associated with intake of potatoe chips, potatoes, sugar sweetened beverages, processed and unprocessed red meats & inversely associated w/intake of vegetables, whole grains, fruits, nuts, and yogurt.  Aggregate dietary changes were associated w/substantial different physical activity, alcohol, tobacco use.  Former smokers, sleep(more weight gain with 6-8 hours of sleep) and television watching.", "AssignmentId": "3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "AU3EIPG4ZRRMZ", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "120,877": ["Participants"], "u.s.": ["Participants"], "free of chronic disease": ["Participants"], "not obese": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"], "u.s.": ["Location"], "free of chronic disease": ["Condition"], "not obese": ["Condition"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5", "children": [{"Answer": "Investigations of 120,877 healthy people were conducted in 2 cohorts. Lifestyle factors and weight were taken at 4 year intervals with adjustments for age and baseline BMI. All lifestyle factors, cohort, and sex specific results were similar.  3.35 pounds was gained on average each interval, with increased amounts of potatoes, chips, sugary beverages, and red meats, and inversely associated with increased vegetables, whole grains, fruits, nuts, and yogurt. This change included physical activity, alcohol and tobacco use, sleep, and TV watching.", "AssignmentId": "34BBWHLWHBW98DPH8S8Q0O0T8BCWI8", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5", "WorkerId": "A21DI93ONQ4P6J", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["B", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["B"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5_34BBWHLWHBW98DPH8S8Q0O0T8BCWI8", "children": [{"Answer": "In a study of over 120,000 adults, it was found that in four years, an average of 3.35 pounds was gained. Factors that may lead to this included consumption of chips, sugary beverages and meats, and it was found that increasing exercise and healthy diet may counteract that. ", "AssignmentId": "3WLEIWSYHP2N02GQOQ1YC5JP5B4H2P", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5_34BBWHLWHBW98DPH8S8Q0O0T8BCWI8", "WorkerId": "A1Y22RY2G8RBAG", "Qualification": 0.8333333333333334, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5_34BBWHLWHBW98DPH8S8Q0O0T8BCWI8_3WLEIWSYHP2N02GQOQ1YC5JP5B4H2P", "children": [{"Answer": "A study of adults found that weight gain was related to eating chips, sugary drinks and meat. Exercise and diet may change that outcome.", "AssignmentId": "3YMTUJH0DT1N8PM8SY1BJ3JB0O6T4S", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5_34BBWHLWHBW98DPH8S8Q0O0T8BCWI8_3WLEIWSYHP2N02GQOQ1YC5JP5B4H2P", "WorkerId": "A18V6K2TMWMSWD", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5_34BBWHLWHBW98DPH8S8Q0O0T8BCWI8_3WLEIWSYHP2N02GQOQ1YC5JP5B4H2P_3YMTUJH0DT1N8PM8SY1BJ3JB0O6T4S", "children": [{"Answer": "Adults gain weight from chips, sugary drinks and meat. Diet and exercise.", "AssignmentId": "3X66WABAJX3YLOHY8KXLAFCGWASG37", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5_34BBWHLWHBW98DPH8S8Q0O0T8BCWI8_3WLEIWSYHP2N02GQOQ1YC5JP5B4H2P_3YMTUJH0DT1N8PM8SY1BJ3JB0O6T4S", "WorkerId": "A9BVDYQU2VTIJ", "Qualification": 0.7222222222222222, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3B837J3LDPHTUVBREASYHRYZPQJSR5_34BBWHLWHBW98DPH8S8Q0O0T8BCWI8_3WLEIWSYHP2N02GQOQ1YC5JP5B4H2P_3YMTUJH0DT1N8PM8SY1BJ3JB0O6T4S_3X66WABAJX3YLOHY8KXLAFCGWASG37"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "This text focuses on how changing diet and lifestyle impacts long term weight gain in both men and women.  It specifically discusses how  the \"eat less and exercise more\" mantra isn't a hard and fast rule, because it depends on a lot of other factors.\r\rThe investigators monitored 3 groups totaling 120,877 American men and women (without chronic disease or obesity), and checked in on them in the following time periods:  1986 to 2006, 1991 to 2003, and 1986 to 2006.  There were evaluations at 4 year intervals with adjustments made for differences between participants.\r\rThe study found that, within each 4 year period, the selected people in the study gained (on average) 3.35 pounds each time!  The biggest factors in weight gain: eating a lot of unhealthy food.  Other things that impacted weight gain: exercise, drinking, smoking, sleep and watching TV (unhealthy habits resulted in more weight gain).\r\rThe overall message:  just eating less and exercising more aren't the only things that impact your overall health.", "AssignmentId": "3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "A5R0NQCWSPEJ9", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "long term": ["Outcomes"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"], "lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "long term": ["Outcomes-general"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0", "children": [{"Answer": "A lifestyle impact study carried out between 1986 to 2006 involving 3 groups of 120,877 American men and women without chronic disease or obesity. Every 4years, adjustments were made for differences in participants. Selected people in the study were shown to have gained on average 3.35 pounds each 4 year period with eating unhealthy food being the biggest factor in weight gain while exercise, drinking, smoking, sleep and watching tv also impacting it. It also showed that just eating less and exercising more isn't just a fixed rule.", "AssignmentId": "30BUDKLTXEG3FP8BG8VQP9POWK95EX", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0", "WorkerId": "A14XU2MC4NWN28", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"], "woman": ["Participants"], "man": ["Participants"], "120,877": ["Participants"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"], "woman": ["Sex"], "man": ["Sex"], "120,877": ["Sample-size"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["A", "A", "A", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["A"], "Condition": ["A"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0_30BUDKLTXEG3FP8BG8VQP9POWK95EX", "children": [{"Answer": "A study of over 100,000 Americans showed that over a four year period, the average weight gained was 3.35 pounds. The main factor in weight gain was consumption of unhealthy foods such as sugary drinks and potato products. Increased physical activity can help reduce weight. ", "AssignmentId": "3X1FV8S5JYCIXXJHSU3RTA4ZN9GGVT", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0_30BUDKLTXEG3FP8BG8VQP9POWK95EX", "WorkerId": "A1Y22RY2G8RBAG", "Qualification": 0.8333333333333334, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "B", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["A"], "Sample-size": ["B"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0_30BUDKLTXEG3FP8BG8VQP9POWK95EX_3X1FV8S5JYCIXXJHSU3RTA4ZN9GGVT", "children": [{"Answer": "A weight gain of 3.35 pounds was observed in a four year study. The gain was attributed to eating unhealthy foods (sugary drinks, potato).", "AssignmentId": "3VELCLL3GL4WXL7OAWDK41X7XVKF1P", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0_30BUDKLTXEG3FP8BG8VQP9POWK95EX_3X1FV8S5JYCIXXJHSU3RTA4ZN9GGVT", "WorkerId": "A18V6K2TMWMSWD", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "60+", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0_30BUDKLTXEG3FP8BG8VQP9POWK95EX_3X1FV8S5JYCIXXJHSU3RTA4ZN9GGVT_3VELCLL3GL4WXL7OAWDK41X7XVKF1P", "children": [{"Answer": "During a 4year study, 3.35pounds was gained from eating unhealthy foods. ", "AssignmentId": "3P59JYT76M5D5B7LOKINQOMDGPRT27", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0_30BUDKLTXEG3FP8BG8VQP9POWK95EX_3X1FV8S5JYCIXXJHSU3RTA4ZN9GGVT_3VELCLL3GL4WXL7OAWDK41X7XVKF1P", "WorkerId": "A14XU2MC4NWN28", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["B", "B"], "Outcomes": ["C"], "Conclusion": ["C"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["B"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["C"], "Conclusion-general": ["C"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3YOH7BII0ASNZJF0ILO6R2WST38KV0_30BUDKLTXEG3FP8BG8VQP9POWK95EX_3X1FV8S5JYCIXXJHSU3RTA4ZN9GGVT_3VELCLL3GL4WXL7OAWDK41X7XVKF1P_3P59JYT76M5D5B7LOKINQOMDGPRT27"}]}]}]}]}, {"Answer": "The relationship between weight gain, lifestyle changes, caloric intake (amount of food eaten) and exercise is actually a lot more complicated that one might have previously thought. \r\rA study investigating more than 100,000 people over a period of 4 years in three different segments saw a correlation between aging and specific types of food eaten. On average, participants gained an average of 3.35 pounds. What appeared to have a substantial effect was the increased intake of chips, potatoes, added sugar, unprocessed and processed meat. All of these showed a marked increase in weight gain on average. Increased consumption of vegetable, whole grains, fruit, nuts, and yogurt actually had the opposite effect and showed an decrease in weight across those 4 years on average. \r\rOther lifestyle change such as alcohol use, smoking, sleep, and watching television also appeared to have an effect that varied across participants.", "AssignmentId": "3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296", "WorkerId": "AZYUCL6B0YROY", "Qualification": 0.6666666666666666, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 0, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 1, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "A"], "Outcomes": ["A"], "Conclusion": ["A"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["A"], "Outcomes-general": ["A"], "Conclusion-general": ["A"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX", "children": [{"Answer": "A study involving 100,000 people over a 4 year period, saw a correlation between aging and specific types of food eaten. Specifically, participants gained an average of 3.35 pounds. The increased intake of chips, potatoes, added sugar, unprocessed and processed meat appeared to increase weight gain. Conversely, increased consumption of vegetable, whole grains, fruit, nuts, and yogurt actually showed a decrease in weight across the 4 year period. Lifestyle factors such as alcohol use and smoking appeared to have a varied affect on participants.", "AssignmentId": "3EQHHY4HQTD1Z342M3LEPCA090W5GM", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX", "WorkerId": "A3D8ZG1VV5FO35", "Qualification": 0.7222222222222222, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 1, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 2, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"lifestyle": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["D"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["D"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX_3EQHHY4HQTD1Z342M3LEPCA090W5GM", "children": [{"Answer": "A study was conducted with the purpose of examining the association of how the aging process is affected by specific foods eaten among 100,000 people over a four-year period. Aging and weight gain were seen among those who ate unhealthy foods, were smokers and drank alcohol.", "AssignmentId": "3LEIZ60CDKKKR71JFLMKMZV877S9ZW", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX_3EQHHY4HQTD1Z342M3LEPCA090W5GM", "WorkerId": "A1CYGMPC6W59KK", "Qualification": 0.8888888888888888, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 2, "Education": "College", "Gender": "female", "Age": "40-60", "level": 3, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "A"], "Intervention": ["A", "B"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["A"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["B"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX_3EQHHY4HQTD1Z342M3LEPCA090W5GM_3LEIZ60CDKKKR71JFLMKMZV877S9ZW", "children": [{"Answer": "According to a study, if you drink alcohol, smoke and eat unhealthy foods you will be more likely to gain weight and age faster.", "AssignmentId": "37Z929RLGAT6AAOJIZXTH6ZHE4ETS4", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX_3EQHHY4HQTD1Z342M3LEPCA090W5GM_3LEIZ60CDKKKR71JFLMKMZV877S9ZW", "WorkerId": "A16KMPWYUZO0M6", "Qualification": 0.7777777777777778, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 3, "Education": "Some College", "Gender": "male", "Age": "24-39", "level": 4, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {}, "Fine": {}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX_3EQHHY4HQTD1Z342M3LEPCA090W5GM_3LEIZ60CDKKKR71JFLMKMZV877S9ZW_37Z929RLGAT6AAOJIZXTH6ZHE4ETS4", "children": [{"Answer": "Alcohol, smoking, and unhealthy diet contribute to aging and weight gain.", "AssignmentId": "3H8DHMCCWAW152FER0OCLGQLU3VDK0", "Question": "NEJMoa1014296_3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX_3EQHHY4HQTD1Z342M3LEPCA090W5GM_3LEIZ60CDKKKR71JFLMKMZV877S9ZW_37Z929RLGAT6AAOJIZXTH6ZHE4ETS4", "WorkerId": "AZBZBTTME3HAI", "Qualification": 0.8333333333333334, "Topic": "diet", "Hop": 4, "Education": "High School", "Gender": "female", "Age": "24-39", "level": 5, "branch": "NEJMoa1014296", "Tagging": {"Coarse": {"diet": ["Intervention"]}, "Fine": {"diet": ["Intervention-general"]}}, "Doggos_crowd": {"Coarse": {"Participants": ["C", "C", "C", "C"], "Intervention": ["A", "C"], "Outcomes": ["B"], "Conclusion": ["B"]}, "Fine": {"Sex": ["C"], "Condition": ["C"], "Location": ["C"], "Sample-size": ["C"], "Intervention-general": ["A"], "Duration": ["C"], "Outcomes-general": ["B"], "Conclusion-general": ["B"]}}, "id": "NEJMoa1014296_3LUY3GC630LMZKBKDFQYH52O1V87PX_3EQHHY4HQTD1Z342M3LEPCA090W5GM_3LEIZ60CDKKKR71JFLMKMZV877S9ZW_37Z929RLGAT6AAOJIZXTH6ZHE4ETS4_3H8DHMCCWAW152FER0OCLGQLU3VDK0"}]}]}]}]}]}